Mark Lee B. Ballesteros



+63 928 138 4165 · ballesterosmarklee@gmail.com Rodriguez, Rizal

WEB DEVELOPER

5+ years' success developing and enhancing manual processes and systems into automation. Team-oriented developer that open to suggestions and also giving ideas that makes the project easier and better. Critical thinker and always plans on what will going to the future of the system.

SKILLS

PHP	Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)	Shopify
Codelgniter	Bootstrap	React Js
JavaScript	SQL	Vue Js
jQuery	Firebase	Gatsby Js
AJAX	GitHub	GraphQL
Node.js	WordPress	Tailwind css

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2024 - Present

Freelancer

Developing a website that allows the client to purchase their desired website design.

- Created an online inventory and order-pickup system for A&J's store
- Currently developing a website that allows the client to purchase their desired website design.
 - https://kethro360.com/

ISCALE SOLUTIONS, Makati, Metro Manila

Feb 2023 - Oct 2023

Web Developer

Modified and update back and front-end of maytronics sales-app website, maytronics e-commerce website, mydolphin e-commerce website.

- https://www.maytronics.com.au/
- https://mydolphin.com.au/
- https://maytronics.online/

FIMOBILE TECHNOLOGY INC., Ermita, Manila

Aug 2019 - Sep 2022

Web Developer

Created Shopify e-commerce websites, catalogue websites, crowdsourcing websites, daily health assessment software, and contact tracing software.

- https://harlanboracay.com.ph/
- https://pureliving.com.ph/
- https://www.cherryhome.com.ph/
- https://snowplustech.com/
- https://motiplanet.ph/

ORANGEAPPS INC., Diliman, Quezon City Web Developer

Jan 2018 - Jun 2019

Lead the Manila Waldorf SIS Project Development team and participated in World Citi Colleges K-12 and College SIS System that makes the work of the teachers and admins easier and faster. Responsible in Automated grade computation, Grade Reports Auto Generation and Grades Statistics.

- https://manilawaldorf.orangeapps.ph/landing/mws/
- https://wcc.orangeapps.ph/landing/wcc/

PRIMEOUTSOURCING.COM Inc., Mandaluyong, Metro Manila Apr 2017 – Sep 2017 Web Developer

Trained to use WordPress as a platform to make websites and creating a plugin from the scratch depending on the needs of the system. Learns how to optimize a website using PageSpeed Insights and Media Query for responsiveness of the design.

- https://vidalia.com.ph/
- https://primeoutsourcing.com/

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

STI College Fairview (May 2017)

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Video Content Creator

https://www.facebook.com/Makuri.gg https://www.youtube.com/@MakuriGG https://www.tiktok.com/@makuri.gg